Working at La Familia
wasn't part of the deal.
Think of what you will do
in La Familia as your training,
as your fallback for your family.
They want to settle.
How long will we refuse to settle?
Their offer for damages is quite large.
Why are you talking to the victims?
You do not make decisions on your own
that can put the whole company at risk.
If you can't respect me
in my own company, leave.
But would you look at that.
The past has a habit of coming back.
What do you mean?
When you tried to pin
the blame on me for the fire.
Is that really how you see me?
All I know is that you'll do anything
and sacrifice everything
just for La Familia.
Pa, that's enough.
Mm. Dear.
Have you seen the video?
Yes.
Mama accused me.
She thinks we're behind that video.
What did I tell you?
You shouldn't have
gone back to that place.
Dear, we had nothing to do with that.
I know what you went through
because of that fire.
I would never do that to you.
Your mother, of all people,
should know that.
I know, Pa.
What I'm wondering is…
who would do something like this?
Did they catch the real culprit?
If they did, then why dig up the past now?
I don't know. But, dear…
It won't do you well to dwell on it.
What do you want?
Who's giving you orders?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We're the victims here.
Are you following me?
How much are they paying you?
I can offer more.
If you're smart,
then you should know which side to be on.
Why would I trust you?
You don't have to trust me.
In fact,
you should be afraid of me.
Because you wouldn't want
to make an enemy out of me.
I'll give you time to think.
Don't bother hiding.
Because I'll find you.
Sir, Ricardo won't leave me alone.
He asked me
who's trying to block the settlement.
What did you tell him?
I didn't say anything, sir, but…
this wasn't part of the deal.
This is dangerous.
I don't want to get hurt.
Here. To calm your nerves.
Quit being paranoid.
Lie low for now.
Don't talk to anyone.
Yes, sir.
This is our last conversation. Now, go.
You again?
The protesters are gone.
I've convinced their leader to leave.
-What about the settlement?
-I'm working on it.
I've also told the press to leave.
-Hi, sir.
-Hi, Ms. D.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Ms. D.
Ms. D, any comment about the recent video?
-What's this?
-What can you say
about the allegation that
you're involved in the La Familia fire?
-And you are…?
-Jonathan Martinez.
Citizen journalist.
You may have read my page, Online Exposé.
Like I've said before,
it's a baseless video.
Why don't you answer, Ms. Aragon?
The victims need answers.
Or is it because you no longer care?
We already answered
those allegations years ago.
Have you done any research?
If you had done your job,
you would have realized
that my family was also a victim
in that tragedy.
What was your father doing in the factory?
If my memory serves me right,
your own daughter gave a statement
that the fire was intentional.
I lost my father in that fire!
Now do I still have to dignify
your accusations?
You got what you wanted.
Please escort him outside.
-Take him outside.
-Let's go, sir.
You can't be in here, sir. Let's go.
He has no right.
No right!
Just ignore him.
He just wanted to get a rise out of you.
I want that reporter banned.
I want him blacklisted.
Diana, he won't be the only one
asking questions.
So, now more than ever,
it's important that
you and Patricia are seen together.
You need to show them a united front,
especially since Patricia was
involved in that tragedy.
Have you two talked?
Is she coming back?
Ms. D.
Here are the files from Finance.
I also made a digital copy.
Do you need me for anything else?
Yes.
You're aware of Burger City, right?
Your partnership that fell through?
Find out everything you can
about Burger City International,
especially the board members.
Give me something I can use.
Find me leverage.
La Familia needs them back.
Do you follow?
It's good that you returned to work.
We had a deal.
You still owe me.
I'm not leaving until I get what I'm owed.
Uh, Ms. D, here's the check.
Your first paycheck from La Familia.
I'll be expecting more
from you from now on.
Diana?
Can I talk to you?
You may go back to work.
-I'm home!
-Hi, sis.
Patricia! Wow! You brought gifts!
-Here.
-We have food!
-Where do I put this?
-Finally, food!
Just put it there.
April, I bought the book you needed.
Thank you, Patricia!
I didn't forget about you, Jena.
I got you a blouse for school.
The color suits you.
Wow, Patricia! This is so conservative.
Yes, so you stop wearing
those skimpy tops.
Uh, what's with all this?
Oh, I got my first paycheck, Ma.
Pa? Pa!
What's going on?
-What's all this commotion?
-Pa, this is for you!
-Wow!
-I bought you a new polo!
Hey, this looks good!
Wow, my daughter's a big shot now!
Oh, no! I just bought these
at the flea market.
-Your clothes are all worn out.
-Thank you.
Oh, wait.
-I'll try it on. Wait a second.
-Sure!
How about this? What's this?
-Ah, this?
-That one.
-Oh!
-Um, I bought it for myself.
It's my shoes for the office.
The shoes they make us use hurt my feet.
-Mm…
-What is it, Ma? Is it ugly?
It's just that we have
so many expenses at home.
Um, I also bought you something.
-It's a new bag.
-This is mine?
Yes. I noticed that the zipper
on the bag you use for work is broken.
-Patricia.
-Thank you!
-So? Do I look good?
-Wow!
-It suits me, doesn't it?
-It does! It fits you so well!
-It's a perfect fit.
-My Papa's so handsome!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much.
-Oh, you better eat now!
-All right, all right.
Here.
Patricia.
-Are you okay?
-Yes!
But you look so tired.
You attended work at La Familia,
but you took up another gig, too.
-Do you still get to sleep?
-Of course, I do.
In the jeepney.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Patricia.
If you're having a hard time
at La Familia…
you can leave any time!
Wait a minute, Martin.
Why are you telling Patricia to leave?
Let her stay in the company!
After all, we're lucky
to be doing quite well now.
-You know, we should celebrate first.
-I told you.
-Yes, yes.
-Come on!
-Let's eat now.
-All right, all right.
-Let's go!
-I told you.
So, what are we going to do?
We sank at number two.
We can't magic our way
to be number one again.
I want the partnership
with Burger City to push through.
According to my sources,
their executives are currently in Manila.
Sis, do you think now's the right time?
We're still dealing with the issue
on food poisoning.
We're still working on
the settlement of the victims.
You think Burger City will listen to us?
People are drawing parallelisms
between the fire and the poisoning.
Comments are mostly from social media.
But we all know public perception
can do a lot of damage.
I believe we will reach
a settlement with the victims
as soon as possible.
However, you also need to know
there's someone blocking
those talks with the victims.
There is someone who wants
to take the company down.
Wow.
You mean to tell me this is an inside job?
The investigation is still ongoing,
but we'll know the result in no time.
Ongoing.
In other words,
you're giving us unconfirmed information.
Sis, come on.
That is so unprofessional!
You're releasing unconfirmed information!
What do you want, Ricardo?
For us to turn against each other?
Sis.
Teddy's right.
Why are you telling us that information?
You better back up everything
you say, Ricardo.
And I'm warning all of you.
I will never allow anybody
to take down La Familia.
I assure you whoever is doing this,
that person is going to pay.
So, you mean, Dad,
they already know you're sabotaging
-the settlement?
-What's with you?
Keep quiet!
Someone might hear you.
Well, have you talked to Carlo?
I asked him to move away.
The last time we spoke, he was
so paranoid about Ricardo following him.
But if that Ricardo does know something…
why hasn't he told it to Auntie?
Or do you think
they're planning something?
They're not planning anything,
and Sis doesn't know anything.
You know how she is.
If she does know something…
she would've kicked me out
a long time ago.
So what?
-What do you think…
-I don't know! I don't know!
All I know,
is I can't be kicked out of here.
No one can know what I'm doing
because I deserve La Familia.
Have you done any research?
If you had done your job,
you would have realized
-that my family was also
-Ah, sir.
a victim in that tragedy.
What's that?
Someone left this for you.
-All right, thank you.
-Okay.
Sign one last document for me, please?
Thank you!
-Ms. D.
-Hm?
Here's what you asked me
to do about Burger City.
Mm-hmm.
Wait.
Where's the new information
about Mr. Smith?
I already know everything
that's written in here.
I tried to get it from
all possible sources, but…
Then you didn't try hard enough.
Mr. Smith is an important man.
All decisions in Burger City
go through him.
I understand that,
that's why I checked
with all our departments,
I read and checked all possible sources,
and I even checked on the Internet.
-I did everything!
-I didn't ask for excuses.
I asked for results.
You know, it may seem like
a waste of time to you.
But real success
comes from looking at the big picture,
not just doing
the bare minimum required of you.
I'm still on the surviving stage.
Not the success stage.
Then we have to change that mindset.
I love my life.
Patricia, Ms. D asked to give you this.
Why? What's going on?
Maybe she noticed you haven't eaten yet.
-I'll get going.
-Thank you, Lara.
It doesn't look appetizing.
No.
We won't give in.
We're used to being hungry, right?
-You're still here, Patricia?
-Sis Tess.
Why are you still here?
Some offices want
their general cleaning today.
I still have to clean so many of them!
I haven't even had dinner yet.
Perfect, I have a sandwich.
You can have it.
Oh, no. You have it.
Tess, just take it.
Come on. I'm still full anyway.
Well, I'm on a diet.
Fasting.
Okay. Thanks.
Any updates on Patricia?
She's still at her table.
Would you like me to help her?
Oh. No, no, no.
She needs to learn
that she has to do this on her own.
Let her swim.
She needs to learn.
But, Ms. D, what you're asking her to do
-is really important.
-Enzo…
I know you can accomplish this in no time.
You've proven yourself.
That's what I want Patricia to do, too.
Understood, Ms. D.
This thing is so complicated.
Lord…
I know you've got a lot
going on right now,
but please, help me.
I need coffee!
Please tell me how to use this, Lord!
Come on! Lord!
Lord!
Patricia, put the beans in the grinder…
Really, Lord?
It's easy.
Here, I'll teach you.
Get some water first.
Just a little, okay? Don't put too much.
Just open this top part.
Put the water in the back.
Okay, then turn it on to preheat.
Then grind the beans.
Just put in three scoops.
Press down.
That'll be quick,
then just put it in here.
Right here in the front. See? It's easy.
Oh. It's actually pretty complicated!
For us, we'd just mix it from a sachet.
That's instant coffee.
This is real coffee.
They're Sagada beans, too.
Here's your coffee, ma'am.
About time.
It smells good.
Try it.
They're Sagada beans.
Mm.
Help!
What was that?
It's Ms. D! It's Ms. D!
Ms. D!
Who are you?
Are you okay?
-Ms. D!
-Go after him!
-Go after him…
-Ms. D!
-I'm okay.
-Patricia, are you okay?
-I'm fine. Are you?
-I'm okay.
I'll call the police.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Security?
We need the police here.
Call them. Hurry!
I was having coffee with Patricia.
When we got here,
that man was already attacking her.
Why? What happened?
Someone attacked Diana.
How did that happen? Where is she?
The medic's checking on her.
Patricia!
Are you okay?
-Are you hurt?
-No, I'm not.
Who did this?
Carlo Lozano.
He's the leader of the poisoning victims.
But why would he do that?
From the beginning, he's been the one
who refused to cooperate
with the settlement.
He must be really angry.
But I have a feeling…
someone's pulling his strings.
Well, whoever it is…
they need to be held accountable.
But she was the target.
What did she do?
Why drag other people into this?
But how did he get in here?
He couldn't have gotten
in here that easily.
Unless someone helped him.
-Sir.
-Yes?
I've already sent you
a copy of the CCTV footage.
Okay, got it. Thank you.
Diana.
-Sis.
-Are you okay?
I'm fine. You? Are you okay?
I'm used to getting shoved around
by goons on set.
Ms. D, the CCTV footage is ready.
That's Carlo Lozano,
the leader of the poisoning victims.
Well, there you have it.
You left the door open?
Or did you two have an arrangement?
I didn't let him in!
How was I supposed to know
he was behind me?
Stop playing dumb.
You know him, don't you?
Didn't you two talk when you spoke
to the victims of food poisoning?
And we all know you're angry at Diana.
What? Did you two conspire together?
I didn't let him in.
You didn't let him in,
but you left the door open.
Come to think of it,
you're the only employee
who was left here.
Maybe you were just pretending
to work overtime so you could carry out
whatever you were planning
with Auntie Diana.
Wait.
Why are you blaming my daughter?
Blaming her? Come on.
We all saw the video.
I'm not blaming Patricia.
I just noticed that ever since
she came here,
one thing after another
has gone wrong at La Familia.
-Come on!
-That's right, Dad.
You always make Auntie Diana
look like the bad guy.
That's right. First, when you got
kicked out of the mansion.
Then came that video about the fire.
-We had nothing to do with that!
-And now this!
Before, they were just targeting
her reputation.
Now they're targeting her directly.
Come on!
And you immediately blame my daughter?
Well, you can't blame us
for being suspicious.
Wherever she goes, there's trouble.
And now Diana's life was put in danger.
How far does your hatred
for her really go?
Is this some kind of sick revenge?
You know what?
That's really possible, Dad.
Because we all know
how you treat Auntie Diana.
She's just someone who's a boss to you.
You always think
she's making your life difficult,
unlike us.
Even though Auntie Diana is the boss,
at the end of the day,
for us…
she's still family.
Right, Auntie?
That's enough. Just drop it.
Let the police handle it, okay?
They'll find out the truth.
Let's go, dear.
Come on.
Diana.
Hmm?
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. Benjie is here.
Look, after what happened,
it's not safe for you to be alone.
It's a good thing
I hadn't left the office yet.
Right.
What kept you here so late?
I was just finishing some tasks.
Ah. That late?
Fortunately, my boss is a slave driver.
You know, you should take a break.
I can handle myself.
Are you really like this?
Even after being attacked,
you still won't yield.
That's exactly what the person
who did this to me wants.
To see me affected, to see me weak.
No, I just refuse to become a victim.
Being vulnerable isn't weakness.
And it won't hurt…
to admit that you need help.
You don't have to carry it all alone.
Good night, Ricardo.
Who are you calling?
None of your business.
By the way…
Carlo dropped this while trying to escape.
It should be easy to fix, right?
Whoa.
It's still working.
You just need to power it on.
I wonder what the password could be.
That way, I'll know
who's pulling his strings.
Why didn't you bring that out earlier?
I didn't know what to do with it yet.
That depends.
Depends?
On what?
I have my demands.
Are you all right?
Looks like the blood is draining
from your face.
Listen. Get some rest.
Don't worry.
I'll let you know
what I want from you soon.
Damn you!
You told me to wait for Diana,
to put her to sleep!
Then why did it all blow up like that?
I'm definitely a wanted man now!
That's enough for you to start a new life.
Don't ever show your face again, okay?
If you hadn't blackmailed me…
Carlo, this wouldn't have happened to you
if you hadn't conspired with Teddy.
But why?
Why are you doing this?
Aren't you working for Diana?
Why did you do that to her?
So that she could see me as her savior.
-By using me!
-Mmm!
Come on now.
I've already given you far too much.
Isn't money all you ever wanted?
So if I were you…
I'd count myself lucky.
And disappear for the rest of my life.
Because if you ever come back…
…you will regret it.
You have no idea
what I'm capable of doing to you.
-You still want more, right?
-Exactly!
-Hey, buy some snacks!
-Thanks, but no thanks.
-Come on, it's only cheap!
-Is it really good?
-Wait a sec. Patricia.
-It tastes like heaven.
Is it true that something
happened here last night?
We heard there was an intruder.
Can you confirm?
Look, Harvey…
I'm peddling baked stuffed buns,
not rumors.
-Just asking a question.
-You're rubbing off on me.
Hey, maybe someone in your family
has a birthday coming up.
-My sibling.
-Wait, really? Contact me.
-Okay.
-I take bulk orders.
For weddings, wakes, baptisms.
-Delicious, right?
-Totally.
How about a snack
to bring to your table? Hang on.
-You're good.
-So yummy.
I know, right? So buy some more!
-Patricia.
-Enzo, would you like to buy some?
Ms. D is calling for you.
Sure. I'll just finish this.
Actually…
it's the exact reason
she wants you in her office.
She's heard about your side hustle.
And she's not pleased.
Uh-oh.
Uh…
Any updates from the police?
I'm fine.
Do you want a baked stuffed bun?
As part of the deal we agreed on.
Nice. Just eight to go then.
Aren't you earning enough?
You're still taking small roles, right?
Expenses never end.
And this is just a small business.
Still honest work.
Clean money.
Want one? There's a little left.
Do you really need money that badly?
I've long accepted that
I can only rely on myself.
Because I know what it feels like
to have nothing
and no one to help.
Why don't you just give me
the full amount we agreed on?
Seems like you don't want me here anyway.
Who told you that I don't want you here?
What's your plan
once you've got the rest of it?
I'll use it to pay off our debts.
Once that's done,
I can finally do what I've always wanted.
To become a famous actress.
And when that day comes…
I like it to be because I worked for it.
Because I gave it my all.
Not just because I'm an Aragon.
Anything else you want me to do?
I made that myself.
Uh… please listen, everyone.
Wait a second.
Because of what happened to Carlo…
we decided to talk to you as a group.
We're willing to make a settlement.
But we have a request.
What is it?
We want to talk to someone
who will really listen.
-That's right.
-Yes.
Someone who'll listen.
Do you have anyone in mind?
The one who talked to Elsa.
The girl who saved her son's life.
-That's right.
-Right?
Right? You agree, right?
You! Did you think I wouldn't find out
you stole from me?
-Ma'am, no!
-Admit it!
-My money's all gone!
-Ma'am, I didn't do it!
-You thought I wouldn't know?
-Ma'am, no!
-Look at me!
-I didn't steal anything!
What? You're a liar!
-No…
-Cut!
Okay, come here.
-Patricia, you were so good.
-How are you?
-Are you okay?
-You're giving everything
even in practice.
Thank you.
-Andi, just do it like that.
-Okay, Director.
-Thank you.
-Okay. You can stand here.
Kaori, do the same thing.
-Andi…
-That hurts.
Hey. You were really
crying so hard there, bestie.
You did better than the actress.
Oh. Shh. They might hear you.
I did my best
to gain the director's favor.
I know that
we really want to be recognized.
But you're working so hard.
Are you trying to prove something?
Yes.
What?
That I can survive on my own.
That I'm going to be a lead
and I'm going to be famous.
All my dreams will come true.
Let me guess.
It's because of your mom, isn't it?
Yes.
I don't want to feel
like I need anything from her.
So I really hope I can
bag a lead role soon, bestie.
I want to show her
that I don't need her surname.
Just remember, bestie.
Include me in your plans, okay?
Of course.
Ouch.
-Patricia.
-Yes? Oh.
Good morning.
Do you need anything?
Yes.
What happened to your face?
Oh.
It's nothing.
I just tried a new skincare product.
What do you need?
The victims requested you to talk to them
for settlement negotiations.
Me? Why me?
They warmed up to you
when you talked to them.
Maybe they were impressed by your courage.
And I think
you're the only one they trust.
The poisoning victims agreed
to sign the agreement.
-Oh.
-Oh. That's good.
That's good.
I heard that Patricia
has been a great help
in convincing the victims.
Looks like you've already taken her
under your wing, Diana.
Does this mean that nothing will stop us
from pursuing Burger City?
You know how big
this deal is for La Familia.
Yes. I'm working on it.
-Good.
-I'm sorry, Sis.
It seems we're not out of the woods yet.
What do you mean?
Uh, have you seen this?
Based on the documents I have,
La Familia was on the brink
of bankruptcy for a long time
before the fire happened.
Declining revenues,
mounting debt,
failed expansion projects.
They almost declared bankruptcy.
Was the fire their solution?
Was the factory fire a desperate attempt
at saving the company?
Where did he get those papers?
I'll try to find out.
You better do it now.
Ms. D.
Where's your dad?
Are you waiting for my boyfriend?
Sorry, I'm here, not him.
How dare…
Cut!
My god. What happened?
That's not part of the scene.
Director, I'm sorry.
I was caught up in my emotions.
-Kaori…
-But it turned out good.
Fine, go over there.
Next setup!
-Yes, Director.
-Are you okay?
-Yes. I'm okay.
-Are you sure?
Yes, don't worry about it.
You know, I know a producer
who's planning to produce an indie film.
That film will be screened
at international film festivals abroad.
I think you're fit for the lead role.
Lead role.
Yes. Someone vulnerable but brave.
Someone with a soft heart
but… is also fierce.
Just like that.
And someone who is willing to do anything.
Oh! That's me!
Would you like to audition later?
I would love to.
Okay, that's just
for the sake of formality.
But I'm going to recommend you, okay?
But they only have a small budget
because it's indie.
And we have to start filming
as soon as possible,
so we need to find a lead.
Are you okay with that?
Yes. No problem. I would love to do it.
Okay. I'll message you the details later.
-Okay, Director. Thank you.
-Okay.
-Next setup!
-Bestie!
-Wipe yourself dry.
-Oh.
-You're drenched.
-Thank you.
-What was that?
-I'm going to be a lead!
Oh, wow!
I think this is the beginning
of my road to stardom.
When it happens, you already know it.
-What do I know?
-I'll be able to free myself from my mom.
-Mm…
-I don't have to take
the money she's paying me.
Because I'll be able to earn that amount
and more once I become famous.
Patricia Dela Cruz. Superstar.
I've read all the articles about him.
I've seen all the pictures too.
And this? This freaking resume!
If this is all you have for me,
I might as well have asked
our HR department.
Those are the initial materials
I was able to dig up…
Initial?
So, I should expect more?
Come on, I want what I don't already know.
Anything on Ricardo Salvador
that could take him down.
Everyone has skeletons in their closet.
That's what I need to know.
Not this!
-Go.
-Okay, sir. Excuse me.
Patricia!
-Sir Victor?
-Yes, that's me.
-My gosh.
-How have you been?
I've been well.
Long time no see.
We worked together
on The Two Faces of Eve, right?
-That's right. It was fun.
-I'm glad you remember me.
-Of course. You look slimmer.
-Oh, thank you.
-I'm really glad you still remember me.
-Yes.
Have you eaten?
I'm good. Are you part of this film too?
-Yes, I'm the producer.
-Wow.
I'm also the co-director.
So, join me and have a seat.
Uh, waiter?
Go ahead and order.
They’re still setting up upstairs.
-Oh, okay.
-Yes.
-What should I get?
-Anything.
Uh… I'll just get
iced coffee with milk, please.
Thank you.
-How have you been?
-I'm an office worker now.
-Really?
-Yes.
How's work?
It's all right. I’ve been pretty busy,
but I'm still selling toasted steamed bun.
-Wow.
-Would you like to buy some?
All right, I'll buy some later.
-Where's the director, by the way?
-He's on his way.
-Ah, okay.
-He's just running a bit late.
I need to use the restroom.
Oh, it's over there.
Just keep walking straight.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Okay.
Just put it here, please.
Thank you.
-Your order's here.
-Thank you.
So, what are the details
of the character I'm playing?
-I want to internalize it.
-Ah.
You have a good character here.
Very challenging.
But I'll give you the details later.
Just relax for now.
Go on and try your order.
-Is that coffee?
-Yes.
Mm.
Yes, ma'am?
I'd like to renew my business permit.
How long does it usually take?
Around two to three days.
Because we're getting a lot
of renewal requests right now.
I really need it ASAP.
This is the only free time I have.
Sorry, but there are
a lot of people lined up.
Maybe we could work something out.
Well… I suppose we could find a way.
What is this?
I really need it urgently.
Well, for this…
the process is very fast.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Her name is Patricia.
She'll be your partner.
-This is Jaymark.
-I'm Jaymark.
-I'm Patricia.
-Hey.
Are you okay?
Hey.
I think I'm just nervous.
This is my first time playing the lead.
Where's the director?
Uh… he's just running late.
Why are you just using a cellphone?
That's how indie films
are made these days.
This is a love story,
so people will surely like it.
You two can come up with your own lines.
Huh? Why?
Improv's popular these days.
Your character's name is Cindy.
You're upset with your boyfriend.
He comes over to win you back.
And after that, you'll make up with him.
You'll show him how much you love him.
-Can you do that?
-How am I supposed to show…
He'll take care of it.
-Right?
-Yes.
Now go over there.
You can do this, Patricia.
You can do this.
Five, four, three, two… Action!
Babe.
-Babe…
-You cheated on me!
I don't love her.
You know you're the only one I love.
What?
Get away from me!
Babe, let's talk.
-Stay there!
-Hey, listen to me first.
I'm sick of this! Let's break up!
Babe, what can I do
to get you to forgive me?
I'll do anything to prove
how much I love you.
-Babe…
-Wait, wait…
I'll take care of you.
No! Wait!
Wait, just a second.
-Cut. Cut. Cut.
-No. Keep going.
You want to be famous, right?
-Then just bear it.
-Relax.
What? Wait. This wasn't part of the deal!
-Stop it!
-Babe…
Director!
Oh, come on! Keep going!
-But it's gross!
-Just do it!
-Babe…
-No…
Stop…
I said stop!
Get her!
-It hurts!
-She closed the door!
Patricia, open the door!
Open the door!
Hello, Patricia?
Enzo, help me. Please…
What's wrong? Where are you?
Help me. I'm at the Meridian Hotel.
I'm in room…
-Hello, Enzo?
-Hey!
-Enzo?
-Patricia?
-Patricia!
-Hello, Enzo!
Ms. D! Ms. D!
I said open the door!
Just leave me alone!
Come out.
Let's just talk!
This is just a misunderstanding.
Come out. Let's talk.
-Come on…
-Don't lie, you pervert!
You're making him rape me!
Carlota!
Oh. Yes, sir?
I heard you've been taking bribes.
Sir, are you sure that it's me,
because there's no way I would do that.
There have been suspicions of you
doing some illegal activities
in the office.
Don't deny it, because…
Ah, sir…
Madam was asking for help a while ago…
-I was just helping…
-I'm sorry, Carlota.
Miss, I want to know where my daughter is.
The room number, ma'am?
We got a call from her asking for help.
We need your help!
Did she tell you who she was with?
She didn't mention, Ms. D.
Hurry, please!
My god, you're wasting my time!
Let me see your CCTV. Come on.
Uh, we don't give CCTV access
to anyone, ma'am.
It's our protocol for the guests' privacy.
Protocol? We're trying to save
my daughter's life here!
Which is more important?
Your protocol or my daughter's safety?
I'm telling you,
if something happens to her,
I'll make you all pay!
She won't come out, huh.
Well, if you don't want to go out…
I'm coming in myself.
-Let me go!
-You thought I couldn't make it in?
-What now?
Do it!
Please… I'm begging you.
Please don't do this.
I know you're a good person.
-You don't have to do this.
-I'm sorry. I have to do this.
Stop…
Help…
Help!
Where's my daughter? Patricia!
What is it?
What's going on here?
I'm the director.
What did you do to Patricia?
We had an agreement.
She wanted a lead role,
and that's why she's here.
Help me!
What do you care?
Well, I'm her mother!
She called us earlier asking for help.
Don't be too loud.
Where is my daughter?
What are you talking about?
Help!
-Patricia!
Stop!
Keep her quiet!
Stop it! Give me that!
Give me that!
I got it.
-Keep quiet!
-Patricia!
Hey! What are you doing to my daughter?
Get off her!
You bastard!
You're a liar!
-Ms. D. Ms. D.
-You monster!
-Stop it! Enzo!
-Hey!
Enzo! Enzo!
Enzo… Enzo. Enzo!
You bastard!
What were you doing to my daughter?
-Huh?
-I'm just following directions!
Do you think I'll believe that?
I'm telling the truth, ma'am.
I owe them a lot of money.
They said I can pay with this.
You monsters!
Stay there! Stay there!
Arrest those bastards!
Patricia…
Are you okay? Dear?
Patricia!
Make sure you do a thorough investigation.
-Yes, ma'am.
-It's an important case.
-Copy, ma'am.
-Thank you.
The lawyers are on their way
to the station.
I will make sure they pay
for what they did to you.
I'll sue everyone.
It's fine.
I don't want to make this a big deal.
What?
You'll let them get away with this?
I don't want to see them again.
No, no.
The lawyers will take care of that.
Don't worry.
But…
if we sue them,
I'd be the talk of the town.
I don't want to explain myself
over and over.
And…
I'd rather not worry Papa anymore.
Can you not tell them what happened?
What?
You've been through so much,
and you still worry about your father?
I just don't want to be a burden.
A burden?
Is that what you think?
Dear…
you're not a burden.
You almost got assaulted.
Because you keep making deals with people
you don't fully know.
If Enzo and I didn't come in time,
it would've been much worse.
Do you understand?
I didn't know that would happen!
I've worked with that director
for a long time.
-I thought…
-No, it's still wrong!
It's still wrong to trust him
with everything!
Remember that!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I know it was my fault.
I'm sorry for the bother.
-I'm sorry, I was a burden to you.
-What burden?
You're not a burden.
You will never be a bother to me.
You're right.
I wasn't thinking.
I'm such an idiot.
Do you think I don't tell myself that?
I'm stupid! I'm so stupid!
I'm such an idiot!
You're not an idiot, dear.
You're not.
Mama's here. Mama's here, dear.
Mama's here.
It's done.
It's okay, they're all gone.
They're all gone now.
They can't hurt you anymore.
No more. No more.
You're safe now. They're all gone.
What if I wasn't able to save her?
I would never forgive myself.
Don't you want
to tell your family about it?
It's not their problem to worry about.
I just got fired.
What do we do now?
I am in charge of my life.
I get to decide what I want for myself.
I never do anything right
when it comes to her.
Is this your plan?
To be the next Mr. Aragon.
Diana loves La Familia more than her life.
What do you think
she would do to anyone who threatens it?